ALL NAMES, CHARACTERS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD AND ANIMAL WELFARE
REGULATIONS WERE OBSERVED
What do you want?
To go back…
to the time
before you came up with the special act.
You'll stop me until the end?
You did the best you could.
So,
stop here.
Is that what you want?
You even dug up your painful memories
that have tormented you
and got a fake illegitimate child,
because you want me to stop?
Answer me.
Yes.
I want us to go back,
like nothing has happened.
Because nothing
has happened.
Even if I give up on the special act,
we can't go back.
"As if nothing happened"?
"Nothing has happened"?
What you said here today
will come back to haunt you.
I don't care.
As long as I can stop the special act.
What on earth are you hiding?
What is it that scares you
even more than an illegitimate child?
LEE HWA-JIN
Why did you have to go that far?
I know you made Park Seo-a
spread the video
Ko A-ram backed up to the cloud.
I've been thinking about it,
and it's just too much.
So you weren't just handling
the divorce case.
I wondered how the victims' statements
and the lawsuit
were moving so unusually fast.
It was you.
You won't be able
to escape punishment either,
for instigating those kids.
I don't intend to.
I did something wrong,
so I deserve to be punished.
I don't understand why you're doing this.
Didn't you join Hyun's campaign
because your husband was unfairly blamed
and denied worker's compensation?
Didn't you enter politics
to make things right?
I don't understand how someone like that
could commit a crime
using the president-elect as an excuse.
You know more about me than I thought.
Most lawyers get others
to do the background checks,
but I do it myself.
Just like I did
with Ko A-ram and Park Seo-a.
It wasn't for the president-elect.
It it were,
I wouldn't have pushed
his only daughter that far.
Then who was it for? What was it for?
"Punishment is not what we want."
"We want our family back."
"Revenge is not what I want."
"I want my mom and dad to come back home."
This was your eulogy for your parents
after losing them
to the H Chemical fire in 2012.
You did your research.
Why did you take the divorce case?
Why did you decide
to be on Ms. Cha's side?
What do you want?
I'm not obligated to answer that.
I want the truth.
And I want the truth
to punish those who did wrong.
So the victims
don't turn into perpetrators
Just like the man who got framed
for arson after an unjust death,
Do Tae-hun.
If you're on Ms. Cha's side for revenge,
remember this.
Ms. Cha must already know that.
She gave you the case
to use your resentment
towards the president-elect.
I don't care.
Because after getting revenge on him,
your next target is
Ms. Cha?
Or are you planning to come between them
so the divorce suit ruins them both?
Ms. Cha uses people.
She doesn't get used.
Let me ask you again.
What do you want?
It's been about ten minutes.
My client's waiting.
We might want the same thing.
If you really want revenge…
If you really want a just punishment,
the answer is
the special act, not the divorce suit.
-Once the special act is passed--
-Hey, look.
You don't know how awful hope is, do you?
I've tried literally everything
for the past 15 years.
I've protested, collected signatures
on the streets,
everything I could
to get the special act passed.
I was so desperate…
that I even became a lawyer.
There's this thing Ms. Cha has.
We can get the special act passed
if you help me get it.
A thing?
Something that keeps
the Party for Peace and Freedom
under control.
Something like an audio tape
or an accounting ledger.
-If you just--
-Steal it?
You said you tried everything.
So why not try
one more thing?
Are you defying me?
Release U-yeong first.
After that.
So you don't trust me.
I've never had a dad.
So I want to make sure
our child has a dad.
"Our child"?
You told me not to make it anxious.
It was thanks to you.
If I hadn't met you,
my life would've been so boring.
The guy who got arrested
is the father?
Release U-yeong first.
Then I'll do whatever you say.
What if I release him
and you still don't do as I say?
I haven't thought about it.
So you don't trust me either.
LAWYER KANG SEON-HO
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Additional charges may apply.
It's me, Cha Su-yeon.
You must be being questioned right now.
Come to my place as soon as you hear this.
I need to have her sign a paper
agreeing to do as I say
in exchange
for releasing the child's father.
A legally binding document drafted
in the presence of a lawyer.
Once I sign the paper,
will you release U-yeong?
If we can't trust each other,
we have to rely on the law.
We're good now?
The Special Act for
the Investigation of the H Chemical Fire
and the Establishment of a Safer Society,
also known as the Do Tae-hun Special Act,
the vote on it is just a day away.
The Party for Peace and Freedom
has officially opposed the bill,
breaking from
former Assemblywoman Bae's earlier pledge.
Let's hear from Noh Cheol-jae,
the floor leader of the party.
We've never changed our party's stance.
We just corrected the improper deal
former Assemblywoman Bae made
in return for the prime minister position.
It hasn't been long
since the election ended.
What we need to do now is
unite the divided people,
not divide the nation
by bringing up the special act
and playing the blame game.
Tell me, how does that serve
our national interest?
Will your party officially
oppose the special act?
Well…
We've got to do what we've got to do.
Although,
there will be another meeting
before tomorrow's vote.
That's it for today.
-Sir.
-A quick word, please.
There is growing attention on whether
the president-elect's
first campaign pledge will fall through.
You did the best you could.
So,
stop here.
Ms. Cha left.
But…
He's stuck in there for hours.
Secretary Shin.
You can't just barge in here.
Don't tell him about our call.
Once he finds out, I'll be fired.
This is Shin Hae-rin.
I have something urgent to tell you.
I'm coming in.
I heard that Chief Secretary Lim
proposed passing the special act.
You're not supposed to know that.
I heard it from Chief Secretary Lim.
What else did he say?
That you didn't accept the offer.
Was that the urgent thing
you wanted to talk about?
You wanted to ask me
why I didn't accept it?
No.
I will get the special act passed.
I'm not asking for help.
I'm asking you to stay out of it.
Secretary Shin.
Please don't forget
why you started the divorce suit.
It was for the special act.
Not for Ms. Cha.
I thought it was President Yu
who was trying to stop it.
So I was trying to protect her from him.
Now you know.
Now you know that Ms. Cha is the one
who has been stopping it!
I need to check something first.
After that--
The one trying to stop the investigation
must be behind the incident.
Secretary Shin.
If Ms. Cha, who was trying to stop
the special act, is the culprit,
she must pay for it.
Only then can we prove
Do Tae-hun's innocence.
You know
politics isn't that simple.
I know.
I also know you've never turned away
from a problem with such an excuse.
Are you saying I have changed?
Maybe you have changed.
Please don't stop the special act
just to protect Ms. Cha.
And please don't stop me.
I can bear everything else.
But the 20 years that I have lived for you
going to waste…
I can't bear that.
My wife wants me
to give up on the special act.
She said if I keep pushing it,
she'd expose who I had an affair with.
Lee Hwa-jin?
Did you know?
I did get a feeling
that she was getting the wrong idea.
But it's not true.
She says it doesn't matter if it's true
because Lee Hwa-jin will speak
to the press herself.
She's going that far?
You're right.
I've never avoided anything
because politics is complicated.
But the problem I'm facing now
is extra complicated.
So give me some time.
Time to solve this problem.
We don't have time.
We do, until the inauguration.
No.
I'm not talking about your time.
I'm talking about the time I have left.
I made myself clear.
Don't stop the special act.
SPECIAL ACT
Secretary Shin!
You think I'd just walk away quietly?
One word from me,
and you're done for, Hyun Min-cheol!
Just imagine how many secrets
I know about you from the past 20 years.
And imagine what will happen
once I disclose them.
You have no idea!
Have you lost your mind?
You think you can just throw me out
and get away with it?
Calm down. Let's talk outside.
-Let go!
-Let's talk outside.
-Let go.
-Come on. Talk with me.
Breaking news. Civil war has broken out.
Secretary Shin attacked
the president-elect.
She was cussing and yelling.
It was no joke.
She was the top contributor.
I'm not surprised.
PARTICIPATION NATIONAL PARTY
The alliance of parties other than
the Party for Peace and Freedom
is already falling apart.
No wonder. The divorce and the affair
ruined the president-elect's credibility.
Some are already calling for
the president-elect to leave the party.
If we push the special act too hard
and it fails,
we'll take the blow too--
Mr. Kwon, let's take a short recess.
What is this?
Sir, what are they saying? Secretary Shin
lashed out at the president-elect?
The vote is tomorrow!
We're at war now. We can't afford
a civil war on top of that.
Goodness!
She's been the president-elect's
closest aide for the past 20 years.
She deserves to be honored
for her contribution, not fired.
This isn't just about the president-elect!
She's seen and heard everything
within our party about the election!
What if she points the gun at us?
Let's hear what she wants.
We have to ease her anger somehow.
Geez, what on earth…
Hello? Assemblyman Choi?
Hello, Secretary Shin. It's me.
So…
I heard something upsetting happened.
Upsetting?
It's not a personal matter like that.
The party won't crumble just because
a low-ranking member like me leaves.
But if the special act gets thrown out,
our party's identity could be at stake.
I just raised my voice a bit,
trying to be forthright with him.
I know. I know how loyal you are.
I understand. I do.
Speaking of which,
it seems like the Party for Peace
and Freedom will turn in favor of the act.
As long as we keep our stance,
we'll easily get it passed.
You must really like jjamppong.
You never go to barbecue restaurants.
I thought you knew that
I stopped going since the fire incident.
Right.
Sorry.
I forgot. Goodness.
Jjamppong is my comfort food.
I don't need to worry
about who grills the meat.
You do that every once in a while.
What about the source
Cha Su-yeon promised to give us?
No news.
But no news is good news, you know.
To catch a big fish like this,
I need to be patient and wait.
That's true.
Right.
You heard
about the new program launch, right?
Looks like they're pushing it
as the main show.
I saw the budget and…
Man, it was a lot.
Speaking of which…
What? Just say it.
You're on the shortlist for the host.
Well, of course,
there are candidates from outside,
and even other networks,
so it'll be tough competition.
But I'm betting on you.
But don't go alone, okay?
We've been working as a team.
Better the devil you know.
Why?
Is being the team leader
for News Magazine not enough?
Come on.
News Magazine is not my program.
It's yours.
And no one can replace you.
So if you're going,
take me with you.
Why me, though?
With your people skills, convincing people
from outside or other networks
would be a piece of cake.
I'm a loyal person.
What is this really about?
We hit a homer
with Cha's wiretapping story.
Let's go for a back-to-back homer
with the president-elect's affair.
Then the game's over.
Whoever's in the shortlist,
they won't be able to beat you.
Counting the chickens before they hatch,
I'm already getting full.
Oh, come on.
That's not what it is.
The universe is sending
good energy your way.
You know how intuitive I am.
Oh, boy.
Look who's calling.
Secretary Shin with no connections.
SHIN HAE-RIN
Sure.
Hello?
I was going to call you.
I heard you quit.
What happened?
Right, that wasn't so nice of me then.
I didn't answer your calls.
You know presidential candidates
declare their assets.
Who doesn't know that?
What? Will you report him
for breaking the election law?
And if declared jewelry gets stolen,
it's a criminal case, right?
Yes, it is.
A simple theft. Nothing more than
a single line in the news. Why do you ask?
What if it's undeclared jewelry
that gets stolen?
That can be a little bigger case.
What if the undeclared jewelry
gets stolen,
and you collude with the thief
to blackmail the president-elect?
Wow.
Just hearing that excites me.
Are you sure, though?
Look into Seon U-yeong
arrested at Haseong Police Station.
Haseong Police Station. Seon U-yeong.
Are you sure about this?
I need to know for sure before I dive in.
Kang Seon-ho is Seon U-yeong's lawyer.
Cha Su-yeon's divorce lawyer?
Does this mean
Cha has Seon U-yeong's back?
No.
She's using Seon U-yeong to join forces
with Lee Hwa-jin, her stylist.
Her and Seon U-yeong are close.
All right. Let me process this.
That's all I can give you.
Cheon is right
about the universe sending energy.
This is my ticket to the new program.
MBS REPORTER KIM YUN-JI
Hi, Min-ju.
See if there's a Seon U-yeong arrested
at Haseong Station.
And write down everything that you hear.
I'll be right there.
Hey!
To MBS, please.
That kind of paper has no legal power.
If you get Seon U-yeong released,
Lee Hwa-jin does anything you say?
What is this, a gift voucher?
Just make it believable to her.
That's what matters.
I'll keep the promise anyway.
Are you telling me to trick Lee Hwa-jin?
It may look like tricking her,
but the results will be the same.
Seon U-yeong will be released,
and the divorce case will be dropped.
A petition is enough
to release Seon U-yeong.
You didn't really
listen to what I said.
Stopping the divorce suit is the priority.
Petition or whatever comes next.
The detention period will expire soon.
Before the arrest warrant--
Whether he's arrested or ends up in jail,
I don't care.
Mr. Kang.
Don't forget who you're working for.
Until the divorce case is dropped,
there will be no petition or release.
Did the president-elect say
he'd withdraw the divorce suit?
It's a matter of time.
Just make sure
that she can rest assured.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll get going now.
By the way, I didn't get to eat today.
Before I go, can I have ramyeon
down in the kitchen?
Ramyeon won't do.
I'll have my butler prepare a meal.
Hello?
Could you prepare a meal for Lawyer Kang?
And more tea for me.
I want to get more rest.
Thanks.
Anything more you want to say?
No.
I'll go downstairs, then.
Let me know if you want more.
Actually,
I was just about to ask
for one more bowl of rice.
My gosh, you must've been famished.
That's three bowls of rice.
Well, I had a lot of things
to deal with today.
Do you not
have a family?
You're always here, you never go home.
I've been doing this since I was 16.
I never had time to make a family.
But then,
you've been with Ms. Cha for a long time.
She must be like family to you.
Family? No way.
She was the first person
to ever treat me like a human.
I used to be called a servant,
but she gave me the title of butler.
I didn't know
you were such a sociable person.
Oh, I apologize.
I went overboard.
No, I like it. It feels natural.
You don't have to stand there.
Please do your thing.
I'll clean up after finishing it.
No, you can just leave it there.
I'll go check on Ms. Cha.
I just made some more tea for her.
Okay.
No legal power?
That's why I came here
before going to Ms. Cha's place.
I thought you should know.
So she lied to me.
But
there's another way
to get U-yeong released.
Please tell me in detail
where and how you stole the necklace.
Why do you ask that?
I'm going to find Ms. Cha's weakness.
Once I find it,
I can
help get U-yeong released.
Trust me.
I will get him out.
I stole the necklace
from the walk-in closet.
Was it in a safe?
No. It was in a display cabinet,
not a safe.
I frequented the place,
so I knew where it was.
Gosh, that scared me.
And the cabinet isn't locked?
It isn't.
What about a safe? Was there no safe?
Oh, I've seen it.
A safe, in the dressing room.
When I took out the necklace
from the cabinet,
I saw a button under the shelf.
When I pressed the button,
the wall slid open.
Please enter your password.
I need to know the password.
Most of Ms. Cha's passwords,
including her phone,
are 1119.
Ji-yu's birthday.
Wrong password.
Please try again.
After three failed attempts,
you cannot re-enter for an hour.
One hour?
It's over if it gets locked for an hour.
Is it six digits, not four?
My electronic door lock is six digits too.
Except for one and nine…
Zero.
I just need to combine them.
Most of Ms. Cha's passwords,
including her phone,
are 1119.
Ji-yu's birthday.
It's Ji-yu's birthday.
Ji-yu is a freshman in high school,
so she's 17.
I'm 29, so she's 12 years younger than me.
That means
she was born in 2010.
If it's six digit…
1011…
Nineteen.
Safe unlocked.
The door is opening.
What were you doing in there?
Shush. I…
I took a selfie
to post on my social media.
Don't tell your mom about this.
Right, and I followed your account.
Make sure you follow me back.
Ko A-ram and Park Seo-a
didn't contact you, did they?
No.
They haven't since they were disciplined.
As I said before, if they come
find you or anything, let me know.
I'll deal with them right away, okay?
Lawyer Kang.
Why did you come back up?
Well, I wanted to thank you for the dinner
you prepared for me.
I ate to my heart's content.
Thank you so much.
Well, then.
I should really get going.
KANG SEON-HO
LAWYER
REVEALING THE PRESIDENT'S HOUSE
He's such an attention seeker.
You must be tired.
I lost my touch from the few days' rest.
Since I wasn't making progress,
it was even harder.
You should eat.
Wash first. I'll prepare food for you.
I just need something
to drink.
You said you could pass the special act
if you had this. Are you sure?
Where are you?
I'll go to you.
I just left the house.
There's a secondhand bookstore
ten minutes from here
that I like to visit.
A secondhand bookstore?
Lawyer Kang, can you hear me?
I don't know
if I should
trust you,
Secretary Shin.
Why would you say that?
"We can pass the special act with this."
There were way too many people
who took advantage of us in the past.
If you use this to strike a deal
with the Party for Peace and Freedom
for your own political gain--
Don't worry.
Did you forget why I went so far
as to break the law and spread the video?
It was all for the special act.
Hand the ledger over to me.
I'm the only one
who can pass the special act.
Someone who goes by Secretary Shin said…
that if she had this,
she could pass the special act.
What? I really don't want to give it
to him, but I'm forcing myself to do it
because my uncle strongly insists.
And you stop me? You're pissing me off!
It's okay.
I'll check it first.
The security regulations say…
Go ahead.
God…
You're so thorough.
You don't even let him
open a bag on his own.
There's no issue. Would you like to check?
HASEONG FOUNDATION
PROSECUTOR NOH CHEOL-JAE…
FINANCIAL LEDGER
HASEONG PETROCHEMICAL
I need an explanation for these.
Secretary Shin claims
that you can seize control
of the Party for Peace and Freedom
with these.
You stole from my wife.
Ki-ju, what did I tell you?
I said we should've
just handed it over to Secretary Shin.
Did you hear what he said?
I knew he would nitpick
saying that I stole them!
I was even prepared to go to prison
in case things went wrong,
and he's acting all unbothered.
I knew he would act like this!
Did you hear that?
Seon-ho couldn't decide
who he should hand those over to.
I told him to give them to you.
For the last time,
I'll let myself trust you again.
If you intend to pass the special law
using those,
drink it up and take them.
If you're going to
drag your feet the way you have been,
just leave without them.
Why me, not Secretary Shin?
I didn't choose you. I was going to
give them to Secretary Shin.
Yoon Ki-ju.
Why me?
You know I suck
at making this kind of choice.
So I used my brain.
"If Tae-hun were here,
who would he have chosen?"
WE ARE AGAINST ILLEGAL SUCCESSION
I heard Lawyer Kang gave you the ledgers.
Hand them over to me.
I'll get in contact
with Peace and Freedom Party.
You want to threaten the assemblymen
and force them to vote in favor?
Of course.
We can't be picky with our methods now.
We must pass the special act--
What if I insist on the ethical method?
Will you reveal my weakness?
I know well that
this isn't how you like to do things.
But at times like this,
you must prioritize the outcome.
"At times like this"?
"The outcome"?
Who decides that?
Who gets to make that choice?
That's why I said I'd do it myself.
Just hand over the ledgers and stand back.
Turn a blind eye.
After the special act is passed,
you can play your role
as the president-elect.
That's what you took me for.
Someone who dumps
all the responsibilities on you.
H Hotel was my husband's pride.
He took me there
even before the construction was finished.
He was proud of building the tallest hotel
using the soil from the lowest ground.
But on the day of completion,
his claim for worker's compensation
was denied,
and he was investigated
for injury by professional negligence.
What I've done for the past 20 years
isn't any different.
I served you like your shadow
from the lowest place
and made you president in the end.
Please stay someone
I can be proud of.
You're the president now.
Do what you must as the president.
This should be my job.
Let me handle it one last time.
Your job is already done.
President-elect!
Your 20 years.
The 20 years you spent for me.
I wished I could stay grateful to you
until the very end.
This is my job!
Hand them over to me!
I told you not to stop me
when it came to the special act!
I told you!
President-elect!
President-elect…
Please stay someone
I can be proud of.
You're the president now.
Do what you must as the president.
You did the best you could.
So,
stop here.
"If Tae-hun were here,
who would he have chosen?"
SPECIAL ACT FOR
H CHEMICAL FIRE REINVESTIGATION
FINANCIAL LEDGER
At the Haseong Interchange,
which leads to Yeouido,
a one-ton truck suddenly broke down
creating a massive congestion
around the area.
In certain areas,
cars have come to a standstill,
it's like a parking lot.
The police and the expressway corporation
request that drivers avoid the area
and check live traffic information.
What happened?
A truck broke down.
The police will tow it away,
but it will take some time.
You can't go.
Our security regulations say…
YEAR 2007
-My hand!
-Tae-hun!
Tae-hun, what's wrong?
Tae-hun.
-Call 911!
-Hang in there.
My hand!
Call 911!
-Tae-hun.
Tae-hun.
President-elect.
I did as you said.
Of course.
I confirmed the President-elect's car.
The voting will start in 30 minutes.
Don't worry. He'll never make it in time.
But must we go this far?
The party is
against the special act anyway.
You talk as if you're a politician.
You might soon become one.
I apologize.
Do you know
why Europeans unnecessarily use forks
and even knives to have a meal?
Because they might die
if they let their guard down
and go to a meal empty-handed.
I'm not only good at arithmetic.
I'm pretty decent in world history.
It's not over until it's over.
How many people in history
do you think died unexpectedly
at the last possible moment?
That's how Genghis Khan died.
And so did Napoleon.
Who's to say I won't end up like that?
So don't say another word
and keep
the President-elect tied up in traffic
until the last possible moment.
Today, at the 22nd National Assembly's
plenary meeting,
a vote on the Do Tae-hun special act
will take place.
People are paying attention to
whether President-elect Hyun's
first election promise will be fulfilled.
NATIONAL ASSEMBLY
How may I help you?
President-elect has just arrived
at the National Assembly.
But instead of his usual state car,
he arrived
on a traffic cop's motorcycle,
which is unprecedented.
Congratulations
on winning the election.
We should've paid you a visit first,
but you came here before we could.
From now on, it will be a private meeting.
President-elect made a difficult decision
and came all the way here.
We should have a heart-to-heart
without the cameras.
Instead of meeting the assemblymen
of Participation People's Party,
President-elect visited
Party for Peace and Freedom,
who was having their final meeting
to discuss the vote.
With only ten minutes left
until the voting,
it is presumed
that President-elect will persuade
the Party for Peace and Freedom himself.
If the special act is
still voted down after this,
President-elect will have to be
politically responsible for it.
He's facing a trial.
How dare you barge in here?
You're not the president yet.
Show some respect!
Did you hear that?
You came here to get some pictures taken
and get it on the news.
"I did everything I could."
"The act was rejected
because of Party for Peace and Freedom."
If you intend to spin the story like that,
just kill some time and leave.
We have less than ten minutes left
until the voting anyway.
Ten minutes is enough.
But for those ten minutes,
lend me your ears.
-What is he saying?
-That's nonsense.
Are you hearing yourself?
-You're being unreasonable.
-What on earth?
What does he want to say?
In ten minutes at that?
I'd like to thank Party Leader Ju Hyuk-rin
for arranging this meeting
so that I could meet
everyone here in person.
Why did you allow him in?
What does he want to say?
I don't think I need to explain why
the Do Tae-hun special act needs to pass.
Just a few days ago,
in the meeting held by
formal assemblywoman Bae,
most of you expressed
that you were in favor of the act.
Instead,
I'll talk about the obstacle
that hinders you
from voting for the act.
You're crossing the line.
What obstacle?
What on earth are you saying?
Do you have proof?
Show us the proof!
What on earth?
What's that?
-What's that?
Are those really…
What do you mean?
He brought the ledgers?
I mean what I said.
That's impossible.
Safe unlocked.
The door is opening.
The late Cha Jin-taek
left this legacy for my wife.
The past records
of your party's slush funds
and the recordings of
some assemblymen's corruptions.
What slush funds?
What corruptions?
If you're here to slander us,
you should go back.
I have eight minutes left.
Eight more minutes
for you to listen to me.
I will return Cha's legacy
to you guys.
It belonged to your party to begin with.
If this legacy
was holding you back
from voting as you wished,
don't worry about it now.
This is the first time
someone has threatened me so openly.
So you're saying
we should vote for the special act
because you know our secrets?
And become your puppets?
There are no secrets.
There are
no copies or recordings.
Really?
But
vote based on
your individual choice,
not based on your party.
The weight your vote holds…
Don't share it
with your fellow assemblymen.
The right and responsibility
of the vote belongs
solely to you.
Don't lay your responsibility
on your party.
Just like how I named the special act
after one person,
for today's vote,
vote as an individual,
not as a party member.
I just want to know.
Fifteen years ago.
April 2, 2012.
Why Tae-hun had to face such a death.
I just want to know that.
Why people try to stop me
from uncovering that day's truth.
And what exactly happened on that day.
I must know the truth.
Did you call Reporter Son?
After the interview,
U-yeong will be released.
No, I didn't do it.
I am President-elect Hyun Min-cheol's…
Is she really your daughter?
Answer me! Is it true?
What if the test results say
Lee Hwa-jin isn't his daughter?
What will you do then?
It's been two months,
and they still haven't found the culprit.
I want to find the culprit
who killed my mom.